They gave him the hands of a killer!
Hands of a Stranger is a horror, thriller film directed by Newt Arnold.
A concert pianist loses his hands in a car crash,
but a surgeon gives him new ones.
The experimental medical procedure goes awry when
the new hands drive the pianist mad.
Dr. Gil Harding, played by Paul Lukather.
Dina Paris, played by Joan Harvey.
Vernon Paris (as James Stapleton), played by James Noah.
Holly, played by Irish McCalla.
Skeet, played by Barry Gordon.
Dr. Ross Compton, played by Ted Otis.
Hands of a Stranger is a 1962 American horror film directed by Newt Arnold and is
unofficially the fourth film adaptation of The Hands of Orlac.
The tone is dark and intense.